[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Neanderthals are the ancestors of modern-day humans.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the daily salt intake recommended by the Scientific Advisory Committee on Nutrition for the United Kingdom?", "correct_answer": "4 grams", "incorrect_answers": ["6 grams", "1 gram", "2.5 grams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are conjugate angles?", "correct_answer": "Two angles that add up to 360 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["Two angles that add up to 90 degrees", "Two angles that add up to 180 degrees", "Two angles that add up to 0 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Proof was originally a play about a brilliant mathematician who worries about inheriting her fathers insanity. Which actress was the star of the 2005 movie of the same name?", "correct_answer": "Gwyneth Platrow", "incorrect_answers": ["Kate Blanchett", "Claire Danes", "Kirsten Dunst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Build it, and he will come is a quote from this drama movie.", "correct_answer": "Field of Dreams", "incorrect_answers": ["Bad News Bears", "Angels In the Outfield", "The Spirit of the Yankees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Point Breakcharacter Bodhi often spoke of the 50-year storm, a climatic event that happens twice a century when a vicious current comes to the coast of Australia from where?", "correct_answer": "Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hawaiian Islands", "South America", "Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Besides Orson Welles with Citizen Kane, who is the only lead actor of a Top Ten American classic who also (co-)directed the film he starred in?", "correct_answer": "Gene Kelly  - Singin in the Rain", "incorrect_answers": ["John Huston - The African Queen", "Alfred Hitchcock - Psycho", "Woody Allen - Annie Hall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the active volcano Koryaksky located?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ukraine", "Latvia", "Poland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Forrests favorite book in the movie Forrest Gump?", "correct_answer": "Curious George", "incorrect_answers": ["Cat in the Hat", "Alice in Wonderland", "The Chronicles of Narnia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bens dream in the movie 21 is to transfer to this school.", "correct_answer": "Harvard School of Medicine", "incorrect_answers": ["Yale Law School", "Berkley Law School", "Stanford School of Medicine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The halting problem computability theory was solved in what year?", "correct_answer": "It cannot be solved for all possible cases.", "incorrect_answers": ["1937", "1956", "1980"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the surname of the detective in the series of movies which featured a Honolulu super sleuth and his sons?", "correct_answer": "Chan", "incorrect_answers": ["Olando", "Lee", "Motto"]}]